Guide to the Terry Tempest Williams Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Papers prior to 2002, 1872-2002 bulk: 1967-2002; Series I
  - Correspondence; Environment; Utah Wilderness Bill; Reviews, 1995
    - TTW Talk-Grand Staircase, 1996 (Box 106)
    - Orion, People and Nature, correspondence, magazine copies (Box 106)
    - News Tabloids, Pages (Box 106)
  - Knick Knacks, 3 (Box 107)
  - Awards and Presentations, 1985-1996 (Box 108 (Oversize))
  - Oversized Materials, 1992-1996 (Box 109 (Oversize))
  - Newspapers, magazines (Box 110 (Oversize))
  - Award and Presentations (Box 111 (Oversize))
  - Books, Newspapers, Correspondence, Notes, 1914-1996 (Box 112)
  - Manuscripts, Correspondence, 1970-1997 (Box 113)
  - Manuscripts, Correspondence, 1995 (Box 114)
  - Correspondence, Environmental matters (Box 115)
  - Memorabilia, News Clippings Manuscripts, 1996 (Box 116)
  - Correspondence, Manuscripts (Box 117)
  - Journals, Correspondence, Manuscript Materials, 1981-1998 (Box 118)
  - Environmental Materials, Manuscripts and Correspondence, 1997 (Box 119)
  - Environmental, Education, Manuscripts, Correspondence, 1943-1998 (Box 120)
  - Manuscripts, Correspondence, Notes, 1887-1978 (Box 121)
  - Correspondence, 1970-1999 (Box 122)
  - Correspondence, Conference, Manuscripts, 1996-1998 (Box 123)
  - Conferences; Environmental and other writings, 1980-1998 (Box 124)
  - Correspondence, notebooks, manuscripts, Teton Science School, 1958-1979 (Box 125)
  - School Projects, Teton Science School, Manuscripts, Research, 1967-1976 (Box 126)
  - Personal, Correspondence, Educational, Manuscripts, 1976-1999 (Box 127)
  - Personal, Correspondence, Manuscripts, 1984-1987 (Box 128)
  - Yearbooks, Nature Book, 1971-1973 (Box 129a)
  - Yearbooks, Nature Book, 1971-1973 (Box 129b (Oversize))
  - Personal, Manuscripts, School Projected, 1973-1994 (Box 130)
  - Newspapers, Correspondence, 1968-1973 (Box 131)
  - Newspapers; Magazines, 1975-1973 (Box 132)
  - Articles; Conferences, 1872-1998 (Box 133)
  - Magazines and Newspapers, 1976-1996 (Box 134)
  - Books, 1983-1995 (Box 135)
  - Memorabilia (Box 136)
  - Environmental Concerns, Correspondence, Manuscripts, 1998-1999 (Box 137)
  - Correspondence, Manuscripts, 1988-1999 (Box 138)
  - Manuscript Drafts for Leap, 1999 (Box 139)
  - Manuscript drafts of Leap, 1999-2000 (Box 140)
  - Manuscripts, Conservation, Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 141)
  - Personal, Manuscripts, Research, Correspondence, 1982-1999 (Box 142)
  - Personal, Museum of Natural History, Slides, 1978 (Box 143a)
  - Personal, Museum of Natural History, Slides, 1978 (Box 143b)
  - Correspondence; Manuscripts, 1993 (Box 144)
  - Personal, Manuscripts, Environment, 1978-1994 (Box 145)
  - Children's Projects; Publications, Greeting Cards, 1958-1986 (Box 146)
  - Plant Collection, Trip to Africa, College Notes, 1976-1985 (Box 147)
  - Personal, Correspondence, Manuscripts, 1997-2000 (Box 148)
  - Research Materials, Publications, 1977-2000 (Box 149)
  - Correspondence, Manuscript Drafts (Box 150)
  - Correspondence, Manuscripts, 1977-1997 (Box 151)
  - TTW Articles; Published Materials, 1978-1996 (Box 152)
  - Nairobi clippings and correspondence, other papers, printed ephemera (Box 153)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted fragile material due to mold damage. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Newsletters, notes, correspondence, printed material (Box 154)
  - Writings, conference papers, correspondence (Box 155)
  - Correspondence (Box 156)
  - Navajo Storytelling Notebooks; Correspondence; Manuscripts (Box 157)
  - Correspondence, Organizations, Environment, 1978-1997 (Box 158)
  - Publishers' Correspondence; Speeches; Manuscript Drafts, 1994-1998 (Box 159)
  - Museum of Natural History, Correspondence, LEAP, 1984-2001 (Box 160)
  - VHS Tapes, 1987-1997 (Box 161)
  - Cassette Tapes, Compact Discs, VHS Tapes, 1972-1999 (Box 162)
  - Photographs and Slides, 1991-1999 (Box 163)
  - Environmental, Folklore, Calendars, 1983-1999 (Box 164)
  - Newspapers and magazines, 1898-2001 (Box 165)
  - Photographs (Box 166 (Oversize))
  - Oversized Magazines, 1984-2000 (Box 167 (Oversize))
  - Oversize, 1955-1989
    - Photograph of Terry Tempest Williams, "For Terry...Chuck Williams" (Box 168 (Oversize))
    - Maps, 1955-1979 (Box 168 (Oversize))
      Includes: Coastal Geomorphology of Great Salt Lake and Vicinity, 1979; Fridley Peak, Montana, 1955; and Garnet Mountain, Montana, 1955.
    - Posters, 1989 (Box 168 (Oversize))
      Includes: "Wise Women Working" and "Good Gardening in Sound Gardening"
  - Oversize, 1984-1996
    - The Joan Walsh Anglund Sampler (Box 169 (Oversize))
    - Weaving (Box 169 (Oversize))
    - Chinese Characters (Box 169 (Oversize))
    - The Secret Language of Snow, Book Layout (Box 169 (Oversize))
    - Posters, "The Wild Card, Conversations with Naturalists", 1996 (Box 169 (Oversize))
    - New York Times Book Review, 1986 (Box 169 (Oversize))
    - Signed Posters (Box 169 (Oversize))
      Includes: "Utah Museum of Natural History proudly presents David Quammen," 1996; "International Heminway Conference Writer's Workshop," 1996; and "12th Annual National Storytelling Festival," 1984.
  - Knick Knacks (Box 170a)
  - Knick Knacks (Box 170b (Oversize))
  - Knick Knacks (Box 170c)
  - Knick Knacks (Box 170)
  - Knick Knacks (Box 170e)
  - Appearances, correspondence, declined events, and writings about Williams, 2002 (Box 171)
- Papers chiefly after 2002, 1940s-2011 bulk: 2002-2011
  Arrangement
  Roughly organized into the following groupings: Writings, Journals and Notebooks, Correspondence, Subject files and Miscellaneous papers, Photographs, Printed materials, Awards, Arwork and objects, Audiovisual materials, Restricted fragile, and Restricted papers. Because the papers received minimal arrangement below the box level, various types of materials can be found in multiple categories.
  - Writings
    - The Woman Who Stares At Bosch, 1997; Highway 128 file; Oh Beautiful Girl unpublished manuscript; Mimi file; childhood file; day book, November 1995; correspondence, 1960s-1980s; magazines, circa 1960s-1990s (Box 172)
    - Alphabetical files of friends and celebrities; The Circle of Moon Whales manuscript; Leap notebook, 1998; Refuge adapted and staged by Gloria Baxter; precious letters; mother's birth cap, 1970s, 1990s (Box 173)
    - Various writings, correspondence, printed material, maps, journals, photographs, Spanish language learning material, 1984-2001 (Box 174)
    - Leap manuscripts and proofs; "Refuge" adopted for the stage by Gloria Baxter script; production photos of "Refuge" the play; Cataract Canyon 2008 trip notes and research material; Desolation Canyon trip 1990 field notes and photographs; Arctic National Wildlife Refuge printed material; material on Utah's rivers; correspondence; bug exoskeleton, circa 1990-2008 (Box 175)
    - Printed material on Bosch, early draft of "Leap", other printed manuscripts, lecture notes, student papers, correspondence, photo essay and poem, 1993-2008 (Box 176)
    - Manuscripts, including "Oh, you beautiful girl", circa 1994-1995 (Box 177)
    - Clippings, correspondence, Red draft, A Voice in the Wilderness draft, A Desert Reader draft, writings, circa 1996-2006 (Box 178)
    - Printed material, writings, watercolors, 1997-1998 (Box 179)
    - "Finding Beauty in a Broken World" manuscripts, printed material, circa 1997-2004 (Box 180)
    - Prairie Dog Squad, Mosaic, Colorado maps, 1998-2001 (Box 181)
    - "Red", manuscript; "Refuge", manuscript; ephemera; correspondence, 1999-2001 (Box 182)
    - Subject files, correspondence, printed materials, photocopies, corrected draft of "Home Work", page proofs for "Red", circa 1999-2010 (Box 183)
    - Manuscripts, printed material, magazines, news clippings, Leap drafts, 2000-2005 (Box 184)
    - General manuscript material, magazines, periodicals, publicity, Bateson's Mosaic students, 2001-2005 (Box 185)
    - Prairie Dog Squad, Mosaic drafts, circa 2001-2008 (Box 186)
    - Printed materials, lecture notes, second pass corrected proof of "Finding Beauty", Strategic Withdrawal published Easter 2002 by Tom and Judy Taylor, wooden keepsake box, circa 2001-2008 (Box 187)
    - Manuscripts, maps, travel material, 2002-2003 (Box 188)
    - Dartmouth lectures; correspondence; printed journals; Diary of an Unwanted War; notebooks; email correspondence; conference notes; "The Open Space of Democracy" original manuscript, circa 2002-2004 (Box 189)
    - Murie Center material, news clippings, ephemera, correspondence, printed material, writings, Refuge draft, circa 2002-2006 (Box 190)
    - Manuscripts from published articles, short story by Cate Williams, agendas and meeting materials, 2002-2007 (Box 191)
    - Manuscripts, maps, travel material, clippings, 2002-2009 (Box 192)
    - Arctic National Wildlife Refuge writings, Dan Frank's notes, Bosch, Hier file, devil file, 2003-2004 (Box 193)
    - Writings, printed material, circa 2003-2007 (Box 194)
    - "Red", proof, 2004-2005 (Box 195)
    - Mosaic draft, printed material, notes, circa 2004-2008 (Box 196)
    - Photographic images from "The Illuminated Desert"; Ecology of Residency notebook; "O" magazine, September 2009; " The Earth:Cost-Benefit Analysis"; "Eagle News - October 2004"; The Illuminated Desert", second draft; Orion Society notes and emails; one deluxe format of "Earthly Messengers" with hand drawn postcard correspondence from Hal Douglas Himes; Presidential Lecture speech notes University of Montana, September 2008; newspapers; "Mangrove Review", Spring 2008, circa 2004-2009 (Box 197)
    - Prayer Dog notes, 2005; Prairie Dog notes, 2004; Prairie Dog Squad 2004; Day Book; "Mosaic" manuscript draft, January 2008; "Oil and Water" by Mei Mei Evans, manuscript draft, 2010, 2004-2010 (Box 198)
    - Writings, printed material, 2005-2008 (Box 199)
    - Writings, talks, printed material, circa 2005-2010 (Box 200)
    - "The Illuminated Desert" page proofs, lecture poster, 2006, 2010 (Box 200a (Oversize))
    - Manuscripts including "Prayer Dogs", "Mosaic", "Finding Beauty in a Broken World", 2007-2009 (Box 201)
    - "Mosaic: Finding Beauty in a Broken World" manuscript corrections, circa 2008 (Box 202)
    - Mosaic draft, circa 2008 (Box 203)
    - "Finding Beauty in a Broken World", proofs, circa 2008 (Box 204)
    - "Mosaic" January 2008 draft, "Mosaic" March 2008 final copy edit, "Leap" manuscripts, correspondence, circa 2008 (Box 205)
    - Page proofs of Wild Birds of the American Wetlands by Rosalie Winard, with an essay by Williams, 2008 (Box Broadside 206)
    - Writings, printed material, circa 2008-2010 (Box 207)
  - Journals, Notebooks, and Day Books
    - Rwanda material, 2006; "Open Space of Democracy" notes and correspondence; photographs; journal, 1988; Wilderness Society Governing Council notes, 1998; personal time line; correspondence; Red: A Journey journal, starts September 10, 2001; Diary of a Unwanted War, 2003; hand-made book, The Dinner party by Hannah Hinchman; 1965 diary; code pink scarf, 1965, circa 1998-2006 (Box 208)
    - Mimi's notebooks, family letters, various photographs and clippings, Turquoise Ledge proof, 1969-2008 (Box 209)
    - Notebook, February 1974; photographs; printed material, circa 1974-2002 (Box 210)
    - Notes, field notes, Italy notebook, calendar, notebooks, Pieces of White Shell (First Draft), slides, 1977-2004 (Box 211)
    - Journals; "Refuge"; day books; Wilderness notebook, 1983-2002 (Box 212)
    - Day books, journals, travel notebooks, 1985-2009 (Box 213)
    - Journals; Vancouver Island notebook, 1986; day book, 1994, 1986-1994 (Box 214)
    - Journals, correspondence, 1989-2004 (Box 215)
    - "Bravo 20 The Bombing of the American West", Richard Misrach; slides from Spain, Portugal, Grand Canyon, Yucatan; photographs; notepad, jottings; Bosch daybook, 1998; annotated "Alchemical Imagery In Bosch's Garden of Delights", 1992-1998 (Box 216)
    - Moving notes, 1998; notes on Bosch; day books, 1992, 1993, 1995, 1997, 1998; Barcelona journal, 1994, 1992-1998 (Box 217)
    - Day books, 1992, 1993; reading notes, 1999, 1995; Journals, 2000, 1999; correspondence; Joseph Smith and the Redemptive West notebook; notes on Japan; lists, 1992-2000 (Box 218)
    - Spain Journals, 1993, 1994 (Box 219)
    - Journal, 1993, 1994,1997, 1998; journal de Espana, 1994; gift journal from Montgomery Fellowship, 2006; notebooks,"Garden of Earthly Delights", "The Open Space of Democracy",The Arctic,Punto; travel log, September 1993; Active Imaginations notebook, 1993-1998 (Box 220)
    - Journal, 1993, 1994, 1995,1996, 1997, 1998; Maine notebooks; travel log, September 1993; writing journal, 1997, 1993-1998 (Box 221)
    - Journals, 1993-2004 (Box 222)
    - Journals, day books, Erotics notebook, 1995-2008 (Box 223)
    - Journals, 1997-1998 (Box 224)
    - Daybook; Spain notebook; The Book of Bosch; Notes de Espana; Leap - A traveler in the Garden of Earthly Delights; El Jardin De Las DeLicias; journals 1997, 1998, 1999, circa 1997-1999 (Box 225)
    - Barry Lopez material, Refuge material, Leap, Journals, slides by Joel Jones, Barbara Bosworth, framed photograph, 1997-2004 (Box 226)
    - Journals, 1997-2004 (Box 227)
    - Uncorrected page proof of "Keeping Faith With Nature" by Robert Keiter; printed material on land preservation; Kathryn Blackett notebook; Mimi's death notebook; notebook split with Dan Frank, May 2009; notebook with water colors at Castle Valley; creative non-fiction notebook, 1999; England notebook, 1997; notebook, 1995; bracelet; political buttons; essay "Retreat", 1997-2009 (Box 228)
    - Journals, magazines, newspapers, correspondence, Bosch materials, 1998 (Box 229)
    - Journals, notebooks, writings, Hemingway research material and notes, magazines, correspondence, 2000-2005 (Box 230)
    - Corrections for "Finding Beauty"; Watts Town; Reading Mosaic; blank postcards from Spain; The Watts Towers notebook; notebooks, 2002; Mosaic class journal, 2002; Italy notebook, 2002; Firenze social forum; Structure notebook; reading notes, 2006; Ravenna, 2002; Mosaic notebook, 2006; fragments built from Gregor Rezzori's library of Santa Maddalena, 2002; mosaic tiles, circa 2000-2006 (Box 231)
    - Notebook, The Edge; prairie dog journal, colors notebook, printed material on prairie dogs, 2000-2007 (Box 232)
    - Writings; Dartmouth, 2006 notebook; photographs; organization files; political observations notebook; printed material; Lesley University honorary degree; clippings, 2000-2007 (Box 233)
    - Conference papers and keynote speeches; Costa Rica journal, 2001; dog sledding pictures; literary journals; correspondence; printed Appalachian ephemera, circa 2001-2006 (Box 234)
    - Various notebooks, Palmyra Atoll field notes, notes, White House Conference on the Great Outdoors notebook, Ted Major's notes on Murie's, 2001-2010 (Box 235)
    - Journal, 2001; printed material; correspondence; photographs, 2001-2011 (Box 235a)
    - Day books, journals, 2002-2006 (Box 236)
    - Day books, journals, 2002-2008 (Box 237)
    - Receipts, 2002; notebooks; Italy-Mosaic; Spanish School; Prairie Dog file; photo negatives, 2002-2009 (Box 238)
    - Notebook, 2005; daybook, 2004; journal; notebook "The Open Space Of Democracy", 2004-2005 (Box 239)
    - Rwanda journals, 2005, Rwanda notes, Mosaic 2008 draft, circa 2005-2008 (Box 240)
    - Rwanda journals, 2005; Rwanda notes; Mosaic 2008 draft; email correspondence, circa 2005-2008 (Box 241)
    - Notebooks, political writing, requests for mentorship and writing samples, news clippings, circa 2005-2010 (Box 242)
    - Rwanda, 2006; Castle Valley day book, November 2008; news clippings; lectures; talks; ephemera; travel Itinerary; email correspondence; printed material, 2006-2008 (Box 243)
    - Rachel Carson visit to Yale notebook; Dartmouth photographs, 2006; notebooks; correspondence; printed material, circa 2006-2010 (Box 244)
    - Field journals Africa, 2007; Namibia journal, 2007; Rwanda journals, 2007; keepsakes, circa 2007 (Box 245)
    - Notebooks, political writing, requests for mentorship and writing samples, news clippings, circa 2007-2010 (Box 246)
  - Correspondence
    - Correspondence, printed emails, presentations notes, Romney family history, circa 1945, 1976, 2002-2011 (Box 247)
    - Images from an art opening, photos, correspondence, journal, 2001, "High Desert Reflections on the Sky" by Chloe Hedden, 1960s-2001 (Box 248)
    - Story of the Wild Horse by Lieus Jack Major; "Desert Quartet" drafts; land deed; fax from N. Scott Momaday; Kamala Chandrarekha manuscript; "Desert Quartet" napkin; Louis's adoption papers, 2009; personal letters; junior high papers and notes; correspondence with Hillary R. Clinton and other White House correspondents, 1992-2000, 1960s, 1992-2009 (Box 249)
    - Various committee and organizational correspondence, committee and organizational printed material, committee and organizational tax material, correspondence and unopened mail, circa 1980s, 1990s, 2000s (Box 250)
    - Family cards, 1980s; correspondence; writings by Paul Grindrod; artist ephemera; Utah ephemera; empty DVD case; clippings, 1980s, circa 2001-2005 (Box 251)
    - Office files, correspondence, newspapers, magazines, 1982-2005 (Box 252)
    - Correspondence, printed material, circa 1990-2008 (Box 253)
    - Office files, correspondence, newspapers, magazines, photographs, 1991-2004 (Box 254)
    - Correspondence, email correspondence, newspapers, news clippings, various organizational and foundation papers, circa 1992, 2003-2008 (Box 255)
    - Correspondence, conference papers, various printed materials, Willamette University folder, Prepublication edition of "Timothy: or Notes of an Abject Reptile", Verlyn Klinkenborg, 1995-2005 (Box 256)
    - Printed articles; notes for talks; Bosch research material; Restoration, Sundance Playwright Lab; Rwanda file; African Rights publications including "Confessing to Genocide", "Rwanda Broken Bodies, Torn Spirits", "Rwanda Killing the Evidence", and "The Heart of Education"; literary correspondence answered for Terry by Monette Clark, circa 1998-2006 (Box 257)
    - Correspondence, printed emails, newspapers, magazines, 2000-2003 (Box 258)
    - Bioneers Conference, October 2004; Murie Center material; "Between Moon and Creek" by DyAnne Korda; personal and business correspondence; printed journals, newspapers, magazines, 2000-2004 (Box 259)
    - Correspondence, notebook, newsletter, circa 2000-2004 (Box 260)
    - Correspondence, letters, cards, post cards, clippings, writings, 2000-2005 (Box 261)
    - Email correspondence from September 11, 2001, fossil (Box 262)
    - Correspondence, journals, "Rewilding North America" page proofs, various committee notes and papers, calendars, printed ephemera, 2001-2003 (Box 263)
    - Correspondence, circa 2001-2005 (Box 264)
    - Business and personal correspondence; literary newsletters; National book awards notebook, 2001; Scattered Potsherds manuscript; organizational and board notes; printed emails, circa 2001-2005 (Box 265)
    - Correspondence; conference files; printed emails; notes; writings; The Robe of Love by Laura Simms, draft copy, circa 2001-2005 (Box 266)
    - Correspondence, writings, printed material, photographs, circa 2001-2005 (Box 267)
    - Magazines, honorary degree, correspondence, cards, manuscript material, "Finding Beauty in a Broken World", 2001-2010 (Box 268)
    - Bread Loaf Writers Conference, 2002; correspondence; printed materials, circa 2002 (Box 269)
    - Correspondence, news clippings, "River of Words" by Frand Canyon High School Students, "Mosaic/Finding Beauty" manuscript, "Prayer Dogs" manuscript, circa 2002-2007 (Box 270)
    - "Walking it Off" by Doug Peacock, uncorrected galley; email correspondence; correspondence; cards, circa 2003 (Box 271)
    - Correspondence, printed ephemera, commencement speeches, magazines, newspapers, 2003 (Box 272)
    - Correspondence, travel receipts, cards, printed ephemera, "Leap" Page proofs, 2003-2005 (Box 273)
    - Correspondence, printed emails, newspapers, 2003-2006 (Box 274)
    - Correspondence, newspapers, catalogs, 2003-2006 (Box 275)
    - Printed emails, correspondence, receipts, printed materials, ephemera, 2003-2007 (Box 276)
    - Printed emails, correspondence, receipts, printed materials, ephemera, 2003-2007 (Box 277)
    - Printed emails, correspondence, receipts, circa 2003-2008 (Box 278)
    - Ephemera, correspondence, travel material, 2004-2005 (Box 279)
    - Correspondence, commencement packets, circa 2006-2008 (Box 280)
    - Notes from lecture at Yale on Rachel Carson, notes, correspondence, cards, 2006-2010 (Box 281)
    - Correspondence from N. Menning; "A Voice for Earth: American Writers Respond to Earth Charter" manuscript draft, 2007, circa 2007 (Box 282)
    - Correspondence, publisher, agents, travel expenditures, 2011 financial information, printed materials, writings, circa 2009-2011 (Box 283)
    - Correspondence, best wishes notebook from Caught in the Creative Act Fall 2009, circa 2009-2011 (Box 284)
    - Correspondence, circa 2009-2011 (Box 285)
  - Subject Files and Miscellaneous Papers
    - Manas newsletter, 1966-1972; 1999 calendar; correspondence; travel itineraries; printed material; photographs, 1966-1972, circa 2003-2008 (Box 286)
    - Questions from Hopi High School students, 2009; ephemera; newspapers; news clippings, 1980s, 2000-2009 (Box 287)
    - Printed ephemera, magazines, newspapers, exchanged manuscripts, 1983-1998 (Box 288)
    - Spain travel material, printed material, photographs, journal, clippings, Yellowstone material, 1990s-2003 (Box 289)
    - News and alternative news weeklies; Great Salt Lake photograph; 1991 calendar; newsletters; note from friend on paper board; multiple contributions to a notebook from The Wilderness Charter School, 1991-2004 (Box 290)
    - Alphabetical subject and name files containing notes and printed material; photographs, circa 1992-1996 (Box 291)
    - Spanish and English printed material, circa 1997 (Box 292)
    - Alphabetical files, clippings, 1997-2001 (Box 293)
    - Printed materials, ephemera and correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 294)
    - Photo collage, "The Open Space Of Democracy" poster, textile artwork, Charles Bukowski poster, two Climate Justice posters, 2009, "Save Our Planet" protest sign, circa 2000-2006 (Box 295 (Oversize))
    - Orion Book Award, printed web pages, correspondence, printed ephemera, 2000-2009 (Box 296)
    - Eugene exhibition file, "A Voice in the Wilderness" draft, Ravenna September 2002 photograph album, circa 2002-2005 (Box 297)
    - Printed materials, newspapers, magazines, circa 2002-2005 (Box 298 (Oversize))
    - Auction catalog, high school reunion memorabilia, magazines, correspondence, 2003 (Box 299)
    - Printed material, clippings, notes, photograph, circa 2004-2008 (Box 300)
    - Printed material, Compton Foundation binder, circa 2004-2010 (Box 301)
    - Clippings, ephemera, photographs, card game, circa 2005 (Box 302)
    - Clippings, notes, printed material, circa 2006 (Box 303)
    - Rawanda trip, Airmed/flying documents, notes, 2006-2007 (Box 304)
    - Clippings, printed material, writings, notes, circa 2007-2010 (Box 305)
  - Photographs
    - Family photographs, publicity photographs, Bruce Hacko photograph, 1940s, 1950s, 2000s (Box 306 (Oversize))
    - Environment Day White House June 1996 photographs; slides case (no slides); photographs of family, friends, vacations, meetings, family cards, circa 1970s-2000s (Box 307)
    - Photographs of family, friends, vacations, meetings; correspondence, circa 1975-2001 (Box 308)
    - Slides, negatives, photographs taken by Brook, 1975-2004 (Box 309 (Oversize))
    - Negatives and slides by Brook, 1975-2004 (Box 310)